OKay the drink we are about to make is called Caribbean Punch.
First thing we'll do is put ice in a glass and measure out one shot of our Banana Liquor.
Find that real quick, here we go.
And, also, one shot of dark rum.
Here we go.
And, some lime juice.
About a teaspoon of lime juice.
Next we're going to add pineapple juice and orange juice.
There's orange juice and pineapple juice.
Equal parts of both.
And we'll mix this up real good.
And there we are.
Bring it up high.
It's going to be a nice beach side drink to enjoy in the Caribbean or in the confines of your own home.
Set up the glass, give it a pour, and the last thing we're going to do is sprinkle a little bit of nutmeg on top.
Oh!
That's a little bit more than a little bit.
Give it a straw and bottoms up!